Guide to the Stanford University Postcard Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Postcards (individual)
  - Kathleen Norris' Home exterior, 970; Tinted Print
    Caption: Home of Kathleen Norris, Palo Alto, California
    Imprint: Pacific Novely Co.
  - A Bungalow Home exterior, 971; Tinted Print
    Caption: A Bungalow Home in Palo Alto, Cal.
    Message: Dear Mrs. Higginbotham, I thought I would drop a line to let you know that I will not be with my class next Sunday, for as long as there is no lesson to teach I am going away on a trip for the day. etc.
  - Palo Alto Residence exterior, 972; Tinted Print
    Caption: A Palo Alto Residence
  - Palo Alto Residence exterior, 973; Photo
  - Palo Alto Residence exterior, 974; Photo
  - house of Mrs. Julia Dyer, 975; Photo
    Message: ...The larger house, on the left, bearing the sign, " The Hamilton" I have a suite of three rooms in the basement on the north side...H.A. Holden
  - Forest Avenue, before 1908, 976; Sepia Print
    Caption: Forest Avenue, palo Alto, California
  - Charter Oak - University ave. and Waverly St., 977; Sepia Print
    Caption: Charter Oak - University Ave. and Waverly St. Palo Alto, Cal.
    Message: Dear...Glad to get your card...
  - train station, circa 1910; 978; Photo
    Dated by cars in image
  - Palo Alto Times Building, 979; Tinted Print
    Caption: PALO ALTO TIMES BUILDING. PALO ALTO, CAL.
    Three months after its destruction, this building was reoccupied by H. W. Simkins, the owner, who cordially invites you to call and inspect his handsome new book store. Special opening july 18 at 5:13 a. m.
  - University Avenue, Palo Alto, California, 980; Sepia Print
  - University Avenue, Palo Alto, California, cars on road, 981; B/W Print
    Imprint: John M. Yanicks
  - Business District, Palot Alto, California, circa 1929; 982; Sepia Print
    before the Hotel President was built
  - University Avenue, Palo Alto, California, circa 1908; 983; Tinted Print
    Caption: University Avenue, Palo Alto, Cal
  - Palo Alto, California, University Avenue, 984; Tinted Print
    Caption: Palo Alto, California, University Avenue
  - University Avenue, Palo Alto, California, 985; Tinted Print
    Caption: University Avenue, palo Alto, California
  - University Avenue, Palo Alto, California, 986; Tinted Print
    Caption: University Avenue, Palo Alto, California
  - university Avenue, Palo Alto, California, 987; Tinted Print
  - A California Orchard in Blossom, 988; Tinted Print
    Caption: A California Orchard in Blossom
    Message: Eleanor dear - Will you"please' drop in and see mama for a few minutes some evening this week?...
    Other Peninsula
  - "Almendral" Fair Oaks (Altherton) San Mateo Co., California, circa 1907; 989; Photo
  - Mountains, 990; B/W Print
    Mountains - Local
  - Mountains, Palo Alto, California, 991; B/W Print
  - The Road over the Mountains to La Honda, 992; Sepia Print
  - A Mountain Road near Stanford university, California, 993; Sepia Print
  - In the Mountains near Stanford university, California, 994; Sepia Print
  - A Mountain Road near Stanford University, California, Feb.-Mar. 1911; 995; B/W Print
  - A Mountain Road near Stanford University, California, Feb.-Mar. 1911; 996; B/W Print
  - The Stanford Hermit, Stanford University, California, 997; Sepia Print
    Domenico Grosso
    People
  - The Stanford Hermit - Grasso, Domingo, 998; Sepia Print
  - Home of the Stanford Hermit, exterior, 999; Sepia Print
  - Home of the Stanford Hermit, exterior, side-view, 1000; Sepia Print
  - Home of the stanford Hermit, exterior, side-view, 1001; Sepia Print
  - Dr. David Starr Jordan, Stanford University, in graduation garment, 1002; Sepia Print
  - Dr. David Starr Jordan, profile, 1003; Sepia Print
  - Dr. David Starr Jordan, standing in quad., 1004; B/W Print
    Imprint: Frank Davey
  - Theodore Roosevelt, Dr. David Starr Jordan, ? Hempl, walking in quad., 1911; 1005; Sepia Print
  - Theodore Roosevelt, Dr. David Starr Jordan, ? Hempl, close-up, walking in quad., 1911; 1006; Sepia Print
  - David Starr Jordan, president of Stanford, 1007; Sepia Print
  - Rudyard Lake, N.S.R., near Jordan farm, 1008; Sepia Print
  - Nearest village to Joardan farm, 1009; Tinted Print
    Imprint: Chapman and Son, Dawlish
  - Bishopsteignton Church, exterior, 1010; Sepia Print
    Caption: Bishopsteignton Church
    Imprint: F. Frith and Co.
  - Widecombe in-the-moor, Nearest village to Jordan farm, 1011; B/W Print
    Caption: WIDECOMBE=IN-THE-MOOR.
    Imprint: Chapman and Son
  - Bishopsteignton Church, interior, 1012; Sepia Print
    Caption: BISHOPSTEIGNTON CHURCH. BITTON STUDIO.
  - Jordan and Evermann plates, fish, Pou, (Cheilinus Bimaculatus), 1013; Tinted Print
    Caption: 236. Pou, (Cheilinus Bimaculatus.)
    Message: This is one of the Jordan and...
    Imprint: hawaii and South Seas Curio Co.
  - Branner's installation, ceremony, back-view, Oct. 1, 1913; 1014; Sepia Print
    Branner's Installation - 1913
  - Branner's installation, procession, Oct. 1, 1913; 1015; Sepia Print
  - Branner's installation, ceremony, side-view, 1016; Sepia Print
  - Branner's installation, procession, 1017; Sepia Print
  - Branner's Installation, procession, front, 1018; Sepia Print
  - Branner's Installation, procession, 1019; Sepia Print
  - Branner Installation, procession, front, 1020; Sepia Print
  - Branner's Installation, procession, 1021; Photo
  - Branner, J.C., profile, 1022; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Davey
  - J.C. Branner, sitting on chair under Stanford symbol, 1023; B/W Print
  - Album of Twenty-Five Views of Stanford University California, 1024; Sepia Print
    22 Post Cards in album
    Post Card Albums
  - Album of Twenty-Five of Stanford University California, 1025; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Congdon and Crome
    24 Post Cards in album. Also a Souvenir Publishing Company booklet, but with Congdon and Crome label
  - Views of Stanford University California, 1026; B/W Print
    12 Post Cards in album, first card loose
  - Views of Stanford University California, 1027; B/W Print
    12 Post Cards in album, first Card Loose [same as no. 1026]
  - Trinity Church in Boston, Mass., exterior, 1028; Photo
    Caption: 4327- Trinity Church
    Boston, Mass.
    Message: i sent a view of this before but this is a better one, showing the farden in front...
  - Trinity Church in Boston, Mass., exterior, 1029; Tinted Print
    Caption: Trinity Church, Boston, Mass.
    Message: About 20 min. ride from my house...
    Imprint: Mason Bros. & Co.
  - San Francisco, Cal, after the Earthwauake and Fire, April 18, 1996, looking up Powell from Market and Eddy, 1030; Sepia Print
    Caption: Looking up Powell from Market and Eddy, San Francisco, Cal., after the Earthquake and Fire, April 18, 1906
    Imprint: M Rieder
  - Capitola Hotel and Beach, Capitola, California, 1031; Tinted Print
    Caption: THE FAMOUS CAPITOLA HOTEL AND BEACH, CAPITOLA, CALIFORNIA
    Imprint: Litho. Britton & Rey
  - Grass Valley, California, group of people, standing in front of building, 1032; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Harold Biggs
  - Grass Valley, California, group of people, dining, 1033; Sepia Print
  - Cow and calf, 1034; B/W Print
  - Oakland Public Museum, exterior, Jan. 1947; 1035; Photo
  - habana, bone yard, campo de huesos, 1036; Tinted Print
    Caption: HABANA. - Bone yard. - Campo de huesos
  - Christmas card-like drawing, 1037; Color Print
    Caption: A Blessed Christmas halleluiah! halleluiah! Let us sing praises to our new Born King
    Message: Merry Christmas and love- I hope to see you January 5th and be able to help you - Marcie Hunt
  - The Ferry Building, San Francisco, California, 1038; Tinted Print
    Caption: The Ferry Building, San Francisco, Cal.
    Message: This is the big ferry house...
  - New Sonoma Valley Union High School, Sonoma, California, 1039; Tinted Print
    Caption: NEW SONOMA VALLEY UNION HIGH SCHOOL, SONOMA, CAL.
    Message: Arrived here...
    Imprint: L.S. Simmons
  - Sonomoa Creek in California, 1040; Tinted Print
    Caption: SCENE ON BEAUTIFUL SONOMA CREEK, CAL.
  - The Hopkins Institute of Art, San Francisco, 1041; B/W Print
    Caption: THE HOPKINS INSTITUTE OF ART, S. F.
  - S.S. "Spokane" in Clacier Bay, Alaska, 1042; Tinted Print
    Caption: S.S. "SPOKANE" IN GLACIER BAY, ALASKA
  - Hearst Hall, University of California, Berkeley, California, 1043; Color Print
    Caption: 345 - HEARST HALL, UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA
  - Wawona Tunnel, looking out toward Yosemite Valley, 1044; B/W Print
  - Stanford home at Michigan Bluff, circa 1940; 1045; B/W Print
    Caption: Former Home of Leland Stanford, Michigan Bluff, California A-357
    Imprint: J. F. Johnson
  - Leland Stanford Jr.'s birthplace, 1046; Photo
    Caption: [In] this room Leland Stanord Jr. was born [M]ay 14, 1864 Sacramento, Calif.
    155 McCurry
  - Vina Ranch building, with 2 workers, circa 1890; 1047; Photo
    Caption: Stanford Vina Ranch, Vina, Cal.
  - Stanford Inn, exterior, 1912; 1048; Sepia Print
    Caption: Stanford Inn [Jan. 9, 1912]
    Stanford Inn
  - Stanford Inn, exterior, 1049; Tinted Print
    Caption: University Inn, Stanford University
  - Roble Hall II, exterior, back view, 1050; B/W Print
    Imprint: Albertype Co., Hyde's Book Store
  - Stanford Motor Court, circa 1930; 1051; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford Motor Court - Highway 101 - Palo Alto, Calif.
    Imprint: Curt Teich & Co.
    formerly Grove Auto Court
  - Frenchman's Lake, 1052; Sepia Print
    Caption: Frenchman's Lake Stanford University
    film negative available
  - Quad, front view, oblique angle, 1053; Photo
    Caption: hand written: University Facade Dec. 31, 1906 [image is pre-quake]
    Message: Dear Joe. As Ever Sam.
    same image as 588, but placed differently
    Quad - Front Views Pre-1906
  - View of Quad from the West, 1054; Photo
    Caption: Handwritten: The Quad Dec. 31, 1906.
  - View of Quad corner, power house stack visible, 1055; Photo
    Caption: handwritten: Power House University Quadrangle Dec. 31, 1906 [image is pre 1906]
    Quad - Corners
  - View of Memorial Church Facade and Steeple, 1056; B/W Print
    Message: Dear Jo. Yours Truly Paul.
    from accn 1998-126; similar image to no. 337
    Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906
  - Inner Quad arcade with view of Memorial Church, 1057; Tinted Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California
    same image as 742, but tinted
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 1058; B/W Print
    Caption: Front View, Memorial Church, Stanford University, after the earthquake, April 18, 1906.
    2006-272; same image as 393 but caption slightly different
  - University Avenue, Palo Alto (looking north from circle), 1891; 1059; B/W Print
    Caption: No. 575
    Imprint: Pacific Novelty Co. (Glosso Series)
    image is oval; card has image of wooden frame on edges
  - House on corner in Palo Alto, 1060; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1496 Waverly and University Avenues, Palo Alto, California
    Message: As it looks now Alice will leave here tomorrow am at 9:15.... Addressed to Mrs. H. C. Peterson, Felton, CA. PM 1911
  - Phi Delta Theta fraternity house, exterior view, 1061; Sepia Print
    Caption: Phi Delta Theta Fraternity, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Students on shore of Lake Lagunita, possibly Junior Day 1914, 1062; Photo
    JMH 8/26/60 written on pencil on back
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 1063; Color Print
    same image as #613 & 614 but different edition
  - Memorial Church (Interior), Undated; 1064; Color Print
    Caption: 34 - One of Center Arches, Memorial Church, Stanford University, California
    same image as #439 but different edition
  - Memorial Church (Interior), Undated; 1065; Tinted Print
    Caption: 10 The Lord's Supper, Memorial Church, Stanford University, California
    same image as #479 but different edition
  - Lake Lagunita, with 3 male students rowing in a boat, 1066; Sepia Print
    Caption: The Lagunita, Stanford University
    Message: these are some new Stanford pictures, which we can make in any desired size
    Has Robinson & Crandall stamp, photograph no. 61
  - Inner Quad arcade (large arch by Memorial Court) with woman in academic dress, 1067; Sepia Print
    Same as #735 but more of upper edge image shows
  - Path along Palm Drive, 1068; Sepia Print
    Caption: In the Arboretum
    Message: Walk along Palm or University Ave - Eucalyptus tree in foreground
    Same as #103, but with different caption
  - View of campus over Lake Lagunita; 1905 library dome visible, circa 1908; 1069; Sepia Print
    Has Robinson & Crandall stamp, photograph no. 53
    Quad - view over Lake Lagunita
  - Greek Theater, Point Loma, CA, 1070; Photo
    Caption: Doric Stoa in the Greek Teater. International Theosophical Headquarters, Point Loma, California. Lomaland Photographic Series, No. 2390
    Imprint: Copyright Katherine Tingley
  - Temple of Peace, Point Loma, CA, 1071; Photo
    Caption: Temple of Peace. International Theosophical Headquarters, Point Loma, California. Lomaland Photographic Series, No. 2385
  - Memorial Church (Interior), 1072; Color Print
    Caption: Interior Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, California
    image is similar to No. 438
  - Old chemistry seen from Quad porch, pre 1906; 1073; Color Print
    image similar to No. 131
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 1074; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Arch, Looking West, Stanford University, California
    same as No. 314 but inferior printing
  - Beta Theta Pi house seen from the street, 1075; Photo
    Fraternity - Beta Theta Pi
  - Oblique view of front of Quad, pre 1906; 1076; Color Print
    Imprint: M. Rieder, Publ. No. 3449
    similar to No. 579 but more oblique angle
  - Kappa Alpha Theta house exterior, 1077; Photo
  - Inner Quad view of Portal, 1078; Sepia Print
    Caption: East End of Inner Quadrangle, Stanford University, Cal. [no] 1899
  - Quad inner, view down aracde, circa 1908; 1079; Tinted Print
    Caption: Arcade, Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: To Guy H. Hunt. How's this for art & beauty? I'm going to finish at Stanford. It's delightful here. Rose & ripening oranges now. Several Cornell men for Profs....Galen
  - Front view of Quad, (from perspective of Chemistry roof ?), 1080; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal.
    Imprint: R. J. Waters & Co. copyright 1905
    No. 16, Richard Behrendt, Publisher (printed in Germany)
  - Front view of Quad, slight aerial view, east end on left side of image, 1081; Sepia Print
    Caption: [No.] 1895 - General view of Stanford University, California
  - Front view of Quad, with cars (and 1 motorcycle) parked on street, circa 1925; 1082; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif. PA-18
  - Front view of Quad from Oval, focus on east side, 1083; Sepia Print
    Caption: Front View, Stanford Univesity, Cal.
    Imprint: Hyde's Book Store, Palo Alto, CA
  - Front view of Quad, urn and lantern prominent in foreground, 1084; Sepia Print
    Caption: North Facde Stanford University Cal. No. 202
  - Memorial Church, view of front from arcade, 1085; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University, Cal. [No.] 257
    Memorial Church (Exterior) Post 1906
  - Palo Alto street scene, 1086; Sepia Print
    Caption: Charter Oak - University Avenue and Waverly St. Palo Alto, Cal S-474
    same image as No. 977 but different publisher
  - Palo Alto street scene, 1087; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1495 - Residences, University Avenue, Palo Alto, California
  - Roble Hall, front exterior, 1088; B/W Print
    Caption: Roble Hall, Stanford University, Cal. [no.] 1844
  - Front oblique view of Roble Hall, 1089; Color Print
    Caption: Roble Hall, Stanford University, California [no. 739]
  - San Francisquito Creek, 1090; Color Print
    Caption: 741 - San Francisquito, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: Charlton & Co.
  - Palo Alto Tree with bridge and creek, 1091; Color Print
    Caption: 433 - Palo Alto Tree, Stanford University, California
  - Palo Alto Tree with bridge and creek, 1092; Color Print
    Caption: "Palo Alto Tree," Palo Alto, Cal.
  - Library Fountain and east side of Quad, circa 1960; 1093; Color Print
    Caption: Campus, Stanford University Palo Alto, California. The University stands on what is known as the "Stanford Farm"....
    Imprint: 251 - Ed Christensen
  - Entrance Gates, circa 1906; 1094; B/W Print
    Imprint: E. P. Charlton
  - Hoover Tower, from Mem Aud, circa 1941; 1095; Color Print
    Caption: Hoover Tower, Stanford University. Former Presient Herbert Hoover, a graduate of Stanford's first class in 1895, has founded a Library on War, Revolution and Peace.
    Imprint: Mike Roberts Color Production
  - Hoover Tower, circa 1960; 1096; Color Print
    Caption: Tower, Hoover Institute and Library Stanford University Palo Alto, Calilfornia
    Imprint: 250 - Ed Christensen
  - Memorial Arch, 1905; 1097; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Arch, Leland Stanford Jr. University
  - Memorial Arch, with Stanford Family Statue visible, 1909; 1099; Color Print
    Caption: No. 120 Memorial Arch. Stanford University, California. Destroyed by earthquake Apr. 18, 1906
    Imprint: Chas. Weidner, Photographer
  - Memorial Church, view of facade, post 1906, 1932; 1100; Tinted Print
    Caption: 6 - Memorial Church Stanford University, California
    Message: Dear Ones all, You may be interested to know that the Chaffee family are in Palo Alto attending Gilbert's graduation....
  - Memorial Church exterior with people in front, circa 1900; 1101; Color Print
    Caption: 258. Memorial Chapel, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Cal
  - Museum, exterior with horse and buggy, circa 1898; 1102; Tinted Print
    Caption: [no.] 1906 - Museum, Stanford University, California
  - Museum, exterior, with extra wings, circa 1905; 1103; Color Print
    Caption: Museum, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: 740 - Edward H. Mitchell
  - University - 3 images: GSB, aerial of Quad and Oval, arcade; with Indian head in center, circa 1970; 1104; Color Print
    Universities and colleges
  - Memorial Church, 1105; Tinted Print
    Caption: No. 6. Memorial Church Stanford University, California
    Imprint: E. L. Hyde / The Albertype Co.
    hand-colored, differs slightly from no. 1100
  - Court yard at Allied Arts Guild, 1106; Tinted Print
    Caption: El Patio de Alfareria (The Court of the Potters). At rear: "The Hands of the Potter," fresco by Maxine Albro.
  - Sally Ride in uniform with Challenger patch, circa 1984; 1107; Color Print
    Caption: June 18, 1983 is inscribed in the record books as a famous first - the first American woman in space, and more popularly known as "Sally's Ride."...
    Imprint: Coral-Lee
  - Cartoon of Stanford along lines of the famous New Yorker cover, circa 1990; 1108; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University / A View of the World
  - Front of Quad from central steps looking toward Hoover, circa 1990; 1109; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University Inner quad at dusk
  - View of back of Memorial Church with Hoover Tower in background, 1110; Color Print
    Caption: Quadrangle. Stanford University.
  - View of campus over Lake Lagunita, circa 1904; 1111; B/W Print
    Caption: From the Foothills to the Bay Stanford University ca. 1904. SU-01
    Imprint: Museum Graphics
  - View of campus from Lathrop estate, circa 1905; 1112; B/W Print
    Caption: From Alta Vista across Lake Lagunita to the Stanford Campus c. 1905. SU-02
  - Memorial Church facade reflected in rain, circa 1903; 1113; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, reflections Stanford University (pre-1906). SU-03
  - Female students in a garden, 1114; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford Co-eds of the 1890s. SU-04
  - Geology expedition group portrait, 1895; 1115; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford University Geological Expedition. Klamath Mountains, California 1895. SU-05
  - View of campus grounds, 1116; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford campus (pre-1888) SU-06
  - Students standing in creek, 1117; B/W Print
    Caption: Student amusements, Stanford University 1890s. SU-07
  - Hallie Hyde in costume holding a fan, circa 1899; 1118; B/W Print
    Caption: Miss Hallie Hyde ("Shocking! Showed my ankle!") Stanford University c. 1899. SU-08
  - Bicycle club outside Encina, 1892; 1119; B/W Print
    Caption: Palo Alto Wheelmen in front of Encina Hall Stanford University 1892. SU-09
  - Encina residents on steps of Encina, circa 1893; 1120; B/W Print
    Caption: Residents of Encina Hall, Stanford men's dormitory c. 1893. SU-10
  - Zoology Club on a picnic, circa 1898; 1121; B/W Print
    Caption: Zoology Club Stanford University c. 1898. SU-11
  - Entrance gates before and after 1906 earthquake, 1122; B/W Print
    Caption: East Entrance gates, Stanford University before and after the 1906 earthquake. SU-12
  - Agassiz statue in the ground after 1906 earthquake, 1123; B/W Print
    Caption: Agazziz headfirst in the concrete Stanford University April 1906. SU-13
  - Damage to Memorial Church facade after 1906 earthquake, 1124; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Church Stanford University April 1906. SU-14
  - Stanford University Concert Band (in costume), 1125; B/W Print
    Caption: Group of early band members clowining on steps of Encina Hall Stanford University 1890s. SU-15
  - Painting by William Keith - Upper Kern River, 1126; Color Print
    Caption: William Keith - Upper Kern River 1876. Stanford University Museum of Art
    Imprint: Printed by H. S. Crocker Co. for the Committee for Art at Stanford
  - Jade sculpture of a water buffalo, 1127; Color Print
    Caption: China, Ming Dynasty. Water Buffalo. Jade, Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Painting of a horse by Gericault, 1128; Color Print
    Caption: Theodore Gericault. Bay Horse in a Stable c. 1814. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Portrait of a lady, 1129; Color Print
    Caption: Francis Cotes Portrait of a Lady 1752. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Painting by J. M. W. Turner, 1130; Color Print
    Caption: J. M. W. Turner Rainbow: Osterpey and Feltzen on the Rhine 1817. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Watercolor painting by Thomas Rowlandson, 1131; Color Print
    Caption: Thomas Rowlandson. None but the Brave deserve the Fair 1812. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Portrait of Earl of Lauderdale, 1132; Color Print
    Caption: Thomas Gainsborough. James, Viscount Maitland, Earl of Lauderdale c. 1780. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Painting by Francis Wheatley, 1133; Color Print
    Caption: Francis Wheatley. Inteior of a Farm Cottage. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Painting from India, 1134; Color Print
    Caption: India, Rajasthan, Kishangarh, 18th century. Radha. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Meissonier portrait of Leland Stanford, 1135; Color Print
    Caption: Jean-Louis-ernest Meissonier. Leland Stanford 1881. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Painting by Roussel, 1136; B/W Print
    Caption: Ker-Xavier Roussel. Women and Children ina park. Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Photograph by Peter Stackpole, 1137; B/W Print
    Caption: Peter Stackpole. Going Home early after news of a fatality. 1935 Stanford University Museum of Art
  - Bierstadt's Bridal Veil Falls painting, 1138; Color Print
    Caption: Albert Bierstadt. Bridal Veil Falls, Yosemite. North Carolina Museum of Art
  - Portrait of Leland Stanford Jr., 1139; Color Print
    Caption: Charles-Emile Auguste Duran. Leland Stanford Jr. 1881. Iris B. Gerald Cantor Center for Visual Arts
  - Page from Horse in Motion by Muybridge, 1140; Color Print
    Caption: Eadweard Muybridge. The Horse in Motion: Abe Edgington, 1878. Iris B. Gerald Cantor Center for Visual Arts
  - Memorial Church (Exterior), 1904; 1141; Color Print